Down!
How you doing?
Hey, watch out, Axel.
Gonna be blowing fireballs after tonight.
Really? Not bad.
Hey, Steve, now that
you're going into the Army,
how about giving my $20 back?
All right, boys.
Hey, take care, buddy.
I'll see you, fellows.
Freddy!
Hi, Mike!
Be good.
Did you hear about the happy Roman?
Yeah?
He was glad he ate her.
Come on, let's go.
Where's Stan? All right.
Hey, Stan, let's go!
Take care of yourself.
Give us a call. Write us.
Take care. I'll see you later. So long.
Okay, bye-bye-
Take care of yourself. Take it easy.
Don't get your ass shot off.
I won't. Good luck.
Okay.
Hey, Mike, take care of yourself. Good luck to you.
Stay out of trouble.
Kill a few for me, too. I will. Stay out of trouble.
Hey, little killer.
Let's go.
Hey!
Hey, Axel, there's Stan. Hi, Stanley.
Hi, Stanley, you asshole.
Hey, Stan!
Get back there.
Stan, it's no use.
Come on, Stosh, you're beautiful now.
You're still an ugly bastard, Stan.
Good luck to you in the Army.
Hey, Stanley!
Come on, come on.
Stosh, let's get the hell out of here.
Come on, Stan. Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
Very mature, very mature,
well-adapted individuals.
Take it easy. Whoa!
Hey, look at that. Let's go. Come on.
Whoa!
What the hell is that?
Where? Oh, yeah.
Holy shit, you know what that is?
Those are sun dogs.
What does it mean?
It means a blessing on the hunter,
sent by the Great Wolf to his children.
What the fuck are you talking about?
No, it's an old Indian thing.
You're full of shit.
Stanley, would I shit you about something like that?
You know, Mike,
there's times when nobody but
a doctor can understand you.
That's an omen, you know that?
You know that we could have one great
fucking hunting trip tonight?
Yeah, Mike, I don't know where the hell
you come up with all this shit.
Hey, wait a minute.
What are you... What, are you thinking
of going deer hunting tonight?
No, not tonight. I'm getting married tonight,
and you fucking guys are going deer hunting?
Hey, first we get you
legal, tuck you into bed with Angela.
Hey!
You guys are all fucking nuts.
Are we mad?
Boy, you're all crazy. Life is over.
Yeah, right.
You're getting married, we're crazy?
It's all right.
Hey, it's all right. We'll be right there.
We'll be right with you. All of us, won't we?
Right? Am I right?
Fuckin' A, man. Right.
Come on.
Come on, you guys, I'm buying
the first round this morning.
Hey, hey, Steven! Steven!
Any, uh, help you might need tonight,
just feel free to call on me.
Ooh!
Hey, Stanley, sometimes your
sense of humor ain't funny.
Come on, Steven.
Willing fingers.
Extra lips.
Fucking A, man.
Hey, you're a regular poet, Axel.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Get in there.
Come on, come on.
I do.
Oh, my God!
I still do not believe this.
My own boy, with a strange girl.
And not so thin, if you understand my meaning.
Not such a thin girl.
The next thing you know, he goes to Vietnam.
I do not understand, Father.
I understand nothing anymore.
Nothing.
Why?
Can you explain?
Can anyone explain?
Pass him on the inside.
You'd never do it.
Shut the hell up.
I'm trying to concentrate.
It's your Caddy against my truck.
Today your lucky day?
You can't make it.
Oh, boy!
You got it!
Hey, Axel, you opened the window.
Mike!
Hey. mighty Mike!
Oh, Axel!
Here's your truck back.
Oh, hell!
Wouldn't wanna take advantage of you.
I hope you didn't break an axle. Axle!
It's a million-to-one shot against a sure thing.
There's no such thing as a sure thing.
Did you see that?
Hey, how're you doing?
Don't take anybody's money.
Don't take my money. Take his money.
Give my friends down here my warm regards.
Hey, I got $100
says the Eagles never cross the 50 in the next half.
And the Steelers win by what? 20.
I got an extra $20 that says
the Eagles' quarterback wears a dress.
You got it!
Take your money off the bar. Drinks are on the house!
Oh, did I get all wet?
I don't wanna know.
Amy!
Come on, Amy.
You know what,
Joe, maybe we could use some more flags.
Is that all right?
Uh,
up a bit, I would say. Wouldn't you say so?
No, no, down.
Oh, it's a beautiful cake.
You've earned a drink.
You have a beautiful cake.
I haven't forgotten about you.
I have one for you, too.
Go to... Fucking hell.
I'll give every car in the town a flat tire.
Every goddamned one.
Oh, daddy!
I'll do it.
I fucking mean what I say, girl. Shh.
Come on.
All around, like a sea. Oh, my God!
Ocean of flat tires.
Fucking... No.
Bitch!
All bitches.
I hate them.
Daddy.
Daddy, no, it's me.
Fucking bitches.
Give them all flat tires.
That's great.
Now, I'm gonna smoke your ass.
It's my shot, right?
Come on, John. Wipe off the tables.
This is it. This is really it.
I mean, here I go.
There's no sense in getting too relaxed, buddy.
Come on.
You faggot.
Hey!
Jesus Christ!
To do this to your own mother,
who prays for you all her life.
Is your heart so cruel, so unfeeling?
You marry this girl, you leave her with me,
and you go with these bums to the Vietnam!
Whoa, whoa!
One flight.
It's one flight upstairs.
When I come home...
One flight!
I love Angela.
And she loves me.
Wear a scarf today.
You don't wear a scarf with a tuxedo.
I'm not gonna wear a scarf with a tuxedo.
You trying to look like a prince?
What do you mean, trying?
You should've done that a long time ago,
that way it would've set.
I know.
Then why didn't you do it?
'Cause I forgot.
Can you still see?
For Christ's sake, Mike. Steven is
getting married in a couple of hours,
I don't know what the hell we're doing
talking about hunting a last time before the Army.
The whole thing, it's crazy.
I'll tell you one thing.
If I found out my life had
to end up in the mountains,
it'd be all right.
But it has to be in your mind.
What?
One shot?
Two is pussy.
I don't think about one shot
that much any more, Mike.
You have to think about one shot.
One shot is what it's all about.
A deer has to be taken with one shot.
I try to tell people that, they don't listen.
You really think about Vietnam?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess I'm thinking about the deer.
Going to Nam.
I like the trees, you know?
I like the way the trees are in the mountains,
it's all different.
The way the trees are.
I sound like some asshole, right?
I'll tell you, Nick, you're the only
guy I go hunting with, you know?
I like a guy with quick moves and speed.
I ain't gonna hunt with no assholes.
Who's an asshole?
Who do you think's an asshole?
They're all a bunch of assholes.
I mean, I love them. They're great guys.
But, you know, without you, I'd hunt alone.
Seriously, that's what I'd do.
But you're a fucking nut.
You know that, Mike? You're a maniac.
Control freak.
I just don't like no surprises.
Damn thing won't open.
Well, give it a kick!
Hey, hey, not like that, not like that.
Here, here, here.
See that?
Fuckin' A.
Unreal.
Axel, now I know why you're not
still kicking for the Steelers.
You know,
I love Mike's car.
Yeah, some cars, they just sit.
I mean, you never know with a car like this
where the hell it's gonna take you.
It makes me feel safe.
Hey!
Axel's humping Mike's Coupe de Ville.
Oh, Axel, get out of there.
Let's get the carnations. Oh, they're over there.
Get up, get up!
What are you doing? Come on, sit up.
Don't pass, Axel!
Here, put this on. You have to have that on.
Crummy tuxedo.
Your tuxedo's been stuck a million times.
Where'd you get this thing?
Fucking A.
You're not funny.
I'm beautiful, right?
No, you're not beautiful.
All set. Thanks, honey.
I'm not... Let go!
Let go!
You can't even sit up, Axel! Oh!
Axel, come on, sit up.
Beautiful. Can't even sit up.
Linda, what's the matter?
I was gonna pick you up.
Hi.
What's the matter?
He hit me.
Don't cry.
Come here, I want to ask you something.
Hey, wait a minute, God damn it.
You don't walk away from me. Nick!
What the hell is that on your face?
Nicky, you and Michael are going
away in a couple of days.
I was just wondering if I
could use this place to stay.
Sure.
I want to pay you both.
And I was thinking...
What are you talking about?
I would want to pay you, Nick.
It's me you're talking to.
How long have you known me for?
What?
Oh!
Have you, Steven,
a free will and a firm intention
to take unto yourself as wife, this woman, Angela,
whom you see before you?
I do.
You have not promised
yourself to any other bride?
I have not.
Have you, Angela,
a free will and a firm intention,
to take unto yourself as husband this man, Steven,
whom you see before you?
I have.
You have not promised
yourself to any other man?
I have not.
Blessed is the kingdom
of the Father and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
Now and ever and unto ages of ages.
Amen.
Whoo-hoo.
Hey!
For a buck, you get a shooter, a cigar,
and a dance with the beautiful bride.
Fuckin' A.
Hey, you.
And you're on your way.
May I have your attention,
please, ladies and gentlemen?
Quiet, please, please.
That's really wonderful, thank you.
May I have your attention, please?
I have a very, very important announcement.
Whoever owns the white Chevy Impala,
would you please move it?
It's blocking the driveway.
Whoever owns a white Chevy Impala,
it's blocking the driveway.
White Chevy Impala.
Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen,
Angela and Steven would like to welcome you
and to introduce you to their bridal party.
And especially to Michael and Nick,
who are also going to Vietnam with Steven,
to proudly serve their country.
You know you did.
Come on.
Monday, Monday's the day.
Monday, Monday.
You're so sweet.
Thanks for being my maid of honor.
Dance, dance.
One minute...
You nut, you want me to dance? You want me to dance?
Hey, Nicky!
Michael! Michael!
Oh, my God.
Nick, Nick, you know... you know... you
know that I'd be going with you guys,
if... if... if it wasn't for, uh,
my knees, you know that.
Huh?
I'm not the greatest dancer in the world.
You're okay.
No, I am not.
No, you're very fancy.
You want a beer or something like that?
You want a beer or something?
Okay. Sure.
What kind of beer would you like?
What?
I don't know. I don't care. Any kind.
I'll get you a Rolling Rock.
Okay.
It's a good beer, it's the best around.
Huh? Yeah, okay.
Rolling Rock?
Yeah.
Be right back.
That's it.
You wanna come? I'll get you...
Hey, Jerry.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Jerry, give us two Rolling Rocks
and give me a chaser on the side.
It's okay. It's a wedding, you know.
You're supposed to let go and have fun. All that.
You really like Nick a lot, huh?
Anybody else for a shooter?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Help!
Put me down! What are you doing? Axel!
Axel, no!
Axel, put me down! What are you...
I'm gonna kiss you.
Axel!
Stop! Stop!
Stab you. I'm gonna stab you.
You wanna fuck or fight?
Axel!
I think I might like to dance
with the lady, if you don't mind.
Have you known him long?
Oh!
Are you having fun?
You know what that son of a bitch is doing?
He's got his hand on her ass.
Its only...
It's only a wedding, Stanley.
What do you mean, it's only a wedding?
Look, he did it again, he just did it.
C'mon, I gotta go get my gun out of my coat.
Go gel your gun, 90 get it.
Whoa, whoa.
Time out. Time out.
You hurt me, you son of a bitch.
You punched me right here.
I'm gonna put him on his fucking ass.
Stan is crazy.
Why? What happened?
There's a Green Beret!
Hey! Whoo!
Jerry, Jerry, give the man a drink.
Hey!
Give him a drink.
Sir?
Sn?
Don't cause any kind of problem.
No, I'm just gonna talk to the man.
We're going over there.
Sir, Mike Vronsky.
Nick.
This is the groom, Steve.
I'm the best man.
We're going Airborne, sir.
I hope they send us where the bullets are flying
where the fighting's the worst, huh?
That's right.
Fuck it.
Fuck it? What did he say?
"Fuck it." "Fuck it."
That's what I thought.
Well, what's it like over there?
Can you tell us anything?
Fuck it.
Okay. Fuck it.
Fuck him.
Fuck it!
Mike!
Hey, hey, fuck who?
Fuck who?
Who the hell is he?
Who the fuck knows?
He looks like a fucking hillbilly.
Give him another drink, Jerry, just the same.
Hey, fuck it.
I caught it.
Will you marry me?
Yeah.
You would?
Mmm-hmm.
What I mean is, if we get back from...
When we get back.
I don't know what the hell I mean.
What goes through your mind comes out of your mouth.
Angela and Steven!
If you don't spill a drop
it's good luck for the rest of your life.
Come on. Come on!
Hey!
Don't worry about what Stan says.
Just forget that. Forget what Stan says.
He's got a big fucking mouth.
That's enough. Come here. Hey!
Give me a crack.
I never really did it with Angela, Nicky.
Great, that's great.
That's my last one true secret.
It's nothing, it's nothing, just forget about it.
Angela!
Oh, Angela!
What am I gonna do when she has a baby?
That's Angela's part, right?
Leave all that to her. Just hang loose.
Hang loose? Hang loose.
What are you so worried about? Be happy.
Get out of here.
We don't wanna see you anymore.
Look at this maniac.
See you Monday on the train.
Hey!
Drive careful.
You didn't know that about Angela, huh?
Right? That's bullshit, man.
Bullshit? Bullshit.
Yeah? I happen to know it's true.
That's bullshit. I happen to know it's true.
You're full of bullshit.
All right, you want to bet? Yeah.
Go, put your money where your mouth is.
Go fuck yourself. Go fuck yourself.
Eh, grow up-
All right!
Michael, what are you doing?
Hey, Mike!
Michael!
Michael, what the hell are you doing?
Fuck it!
Michael, come back here.
What the hell is he doing?
Michael, what the hell are you doing?
Michael, come back here, Michael!
Michael, we love you. Get back here!
I gotta talk to you!
Mike!
Hey!
Shit!
I must be out of my fucking mind.
I must be out of my mind.
I don't know, everything's going so fast.
Man, oh, man!
Hey, Nick.
You think we'll ever come back?
From Nam?
Yeah.
You know something?
The whole thing,
it's right here.
I love this fucking place.
I know that sounds crazy,
but if anything happens, Mike,
don't leave... don't leave me over there.
You got-you gotta...
Just don't leave me.
You gotta promise me that, Mike.
Hey!
No, man, you got-you gotta...
you gotta promise. Definitely.
Hey. Nicky. Huh?
You got it, pal.
It's
the Screaming Eagles Airborne Song.
Bunch of assholes.
Fuckin' A!
I can't remember the rest of the words.
That's okay.
Chickenshit, get scared.
Don't push.
Fucking cold.
36 beers.
Oh!
What?
Come on.
All right, I'll go already. Wait, wait.
Did you ever piss and take a
drink of beer at the same time?
Oh!
I just barely got a chance to shake it off.
Wait! Come on!
Fuck.
Bastards!
Sons of bitches!
You guys going my way?
Come on.
Fuck!
That's not funny!
Don't fuck around, now.
Come on. Don't fuck around.
Don't fuck around.
Let me out!
Out, out. Let me out.
Get out.
This is not it!
Definitely. This is not it.
They changed it. No kidding.
Somehow, they changed it.
Like this happens every goddamm year.
You're full of shit, Stanley.
Who did you say was full of shit?
You're full of shit, you're always full of shit.
I'm starving.
Eat that.
Nicky, let me ask you a question.
How come I never see you eating?
I like to starve myself. Keeps the fear up.
It ain't natural.
Come on, John.
Hey, it's mine.
You really want it that bad?
You're goddamn right!
Hey, give me a Twinkie, Mike.
What are you guys, a bunch of cripples? Here.
That's mustard.
What?
He put mustard on his Twinkie.
You're talking like a goddamn traffic cop.
Incredible.
Come on, give me a beer, Mike. Come on.
I can't believe you guys.
What the hell am I doing with you?
This is not it.
They changed it, somehow they changed it.
You couldn't find your own ass with two hands.
Fuckin' A.
Hey, you know.
We forgot to toast Steven and Angela.
Steven and Angela!
What?
Don't make me laugh when I have things in my mouth.
I can't take you guys anywhere.
What the hell are you doing?
Take your hands off the fucking bread.
You can dress him up,
but you can't take him anywhere.
Come on! Come on! What the fuck are you doing?
That was mine, you assholes.
Fucking assholes. I can't fucking...
Fuckin' A!
You know, Axel,
you got a really terrific vocabulary.
Fuckin' A.
Hey, watch the gear.
Watch the rifle.
Give me my bag.
It's getting cold. Huh?
Hey, Mike, you got any extra thermal socks?
Fuckin' A.
Hey, Mike!
You got any extra thermal socks?
Never mind, I got them.
Where the hell's my boots?
Anybody see my boots?
Somebody took my boots.
I bought them special.
All right.
All right, you guys, whoever
took my boots, I want them back.
I got a boot for you, Stan.
Right up your ass.
Hey, Mike.
Hey, Mike, let me borrow your spares, huh?
Your extra pair?
No, Stan.
No?
What do you mean, "no?"
Just what I said, no. "No" means no.
Some fucking friend, you're some
fucking friend, you know that?
You got to learn, Stanley.
Every time you come up here you got
your goddamn head up your ass.
Maybe he likes the view from up there, huh?
Every time he comes up, he's got no knife,
he's got no jacket, he's got
no pants, he's got no boots.
All he's got is that stupid gun he
carries around like John Wayne.
That ain't gonna help you.
Oh, what the hell, Mike. Give him the boots.
No way. I ain't giving him no boots.
No more, no more, that's it.
You're a fucking bastard, you know that?
Stanley, you see this?
This is this, this ain't something else.
This is this.
From now on, you're on your own.
I fixed you up a million times.
I fixed him up a million times.
I don t know now many times I must
have fixed him up with girls,
and nothing ever happens. Zero.
Hey, you know your trouble, Mike, huh?
Nobody ever knows what the fuck you're talking about.
Huh? "This is this."
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
"This is this."
I mean, is that some faggot-sounding
bullshit, or is that some...
Shut up, Stan, will you?
Hey, man, you're out of line.
Watch out with that gun, Stan.
Do you know what I think?
You know what I think?
There's times I swear, I think
you're a fucking faggot.
Hey, come on, you guys.
Last week, last week he could've had that
new red-headed waitress at the Bowladrome.
He could've had it knocked.
Look what he fucking did? Nothing.
That's what.
Shut up, Stan! Just shut up.
Just shut up.
Take... Take Michael's goddamn boots and shut up!
Otherwise, I'm goin' home.
Okay, I'm going home right now.
Get off my stuff.
What the hell are you doing in there?
Hey, Stosh,
I said no.
What, are you gonna shoot me?
Huh?
Here.
What's the matter with you?
Stan.
Watch it, Mike! Watch it.
Hey, Steven!
Hey, Angela, I got a big gun!
Go home! Go home!
Hey!
Unbelievable!
Holy Christ, I don't believe it.
Mike?
Mike!
Jesus Christ!
Hey!
Take it easy, Stevie!
Stevie, calm down!
Think of something else.
Control yourself. Think of something else.
We don't belong here.
Take it easy. It's gonna be okay.
I'm all right.
Okay. I'm okay.
Just take it easy. Take it easy.
It's okay, it's okay.
Take it easy, Stevie. Stevie, take it easy.
Mike.
Come on. Come on.
I'm okay.
That's all right. Okay.
Okay, all right, press it, press hard, press hard.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
Go ahead. That's it. That's it
Mike?
Shake it off. Shake it out. Shake it out.
Think of something else. Think of home.
Think of home.
Think of Angela.
They're gonna have to kill my ass, Mike.
Stevie, you gotta do it. If you don't do it,
they're gonna throw you in the pit.
They throw you in the pit, you're gonna die.
Go ahead, you gotta do it. You can do it.
You can do it, Stevie.
Look in my eyes. Stevie. Stevie, look at me!
Mike?
Do it! Do it!
Go ahead! Show them you got balls.
Show 'em you got balls.
Fuck you.
Go ahead!
Shoot me. Go ahead.
Come on.
Go ahead.
Go ahead, Stevie! Go ahead. Show them you got balls!
Go ahead!
Hey, kid.
Kid. Look at me, Stevie, you did it.
Stevie, you showed these bastards.
You showed 'em.
Don't worry, kid.
You did it.
Michael!
Stevie!
Michael.
Stevie, don t worry.
Mike, help!
Oh, God! There's rats in here!
Nicky.
Motherfucker!
Nicky, listen.
It's up to us now. It's me and you.
What about Steven?
Forget him.
Forget him?
Forget him. He ain't gonna make it.
Who do you think you are? God?
Look at him, he's in a daze.
He ain't coming out, he's in a dream.
Mike, what are you saying?
I'm saying forget him, Nick.
Get it through your head, or
you and me are both gone, too.
Gotta play with more bullets.
What?
More bullets.
I gotta get more bullets in the gun.
What?
We got to play with more bullets.
More bullets in the gun?
How many more bullets?
Three.
That means we've got to play each other.
More bullets against each other?
What, are you crazy?
Nicky, it's the only way.
I'll pick the moment.
The game goes until I move.
When I start shooting, you go for the nearest guard
you get his gun and zap the fucker.
I'm not ready for this.
You gotta listen to me.
You want to stay down here and die?
Go.
It's up to you. Now, it's up to you.
No!
Hey, him against me!
Side by side.
Get away! Get away!
Man, I can't wait!
Michael!
Come on!
These fuckers, these fuckers. Go ahead, Nicky.
Go ahead, Nicky.
It's gonna be all right. It's gonna be all right.
Go ahead, Nicky. Go ahead, Nicky.
That's it. That's it.
I do three bullets. Three, three.
We do three, huh? One, two, three. Three.
Three, three.
Don't worry, Nick. Don't worry.
In five minutes, we're gonna be out of here.
We're gonna be out of here.
Now we got ourselves a game. You and me. You and me.
Okay. Okay, you want a game?
Go ahead.
No more.
That's fucked.
I'm gonna will us outta here.
You've got an empty chamber in that gun.
Put an empty chamber in that gun. Go ahead.
God damn it!
It's gonna be all right, Nicky.
Go ahead, shoot! Shoot, Nicky!
You motherfucker!
No, no, no, Nicky!
Now you're gonna die, you motherfucker!
You're gonna die!
Go ahead, go ahead, Nicky, just do it.
Do it, do it, do it.
Go ahead.
You made it.
It's all right.
All right, we're gonna show them.
All right.
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Nicky.
Come on, damn it! Come on.
Oh, shit.
Get me up.
Steve!
Get on it. Get on it.
Michael, Michael.
Michael!
Stevie, come on.
Come on, Stevie. We're gonna go for a swim.
Come on, Stevie.
Come on, come on.
We don't belong here in the jungle, Michael.
Just get on, see? Just get on.
There's rats in these waters.
Hold on, right there.
Hold on.
Michael.
Okay, buddy.
Mike.
Nicky.
Mike, I want to go home, Mike.
What is that?
What's that sound, Michael?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Go on! Go on!
Mike! Mike! Hold on, Michael.
Mike!
Steve!
I hit some rocks, Michael. I hit some rocks.
On my legs, Michael.
Okay. Relax.
Come on, come on.
Stevie, come on.
Come on, Stevie.
Please.
My legs.
I hit some rocks.
Okay. All right.
That's it.
My arm.
Okay.
I can't feel my legs.
All right, all right, come on.
My arm.
Push yourself.
Whoa.
Oh, man.
Okay, kid, okay, shh, shh.
Take him.
Not me, him.
Are you Nikanor Chevotarevich?
Can you understand me, Nikanor?
Are you Chevotarevich? Are you sure?
Yes.
Uh-huh, Chevotarevich. Is that a Russian name?
No. It's American.
All right, let me see your name tag.
Is this yours?
It's his.
What are your parents' names?
Lou.
And my mother's name is,
um, Eva.
And what are your parents' dates of birth?
We're gonna have to get him out of here.
Sure, sure, sure.
What's the other
one on the extension for?
Excuse me.
Some more noise, huh?
Hello.
Uh, um, I'm calling the United States.
Clairton, Pennsylvania.
Clair... It's C-L
A-I-R
T-O-N.
Pennsylvania. Right.
I don't want to go home alone.
Never mind.
Nothing, nothing, no. Never mind. Nothing.
Do you understand?
I'll give you a call as soon as I can.
I forgot about that. Yeah, yeah.
Hey, back off, Jack!
Back off.
Yeah, well, just do that.
Mike?
Mike.
Mike!
Hey, Mike?
I'm sorry. I thought you were someone else.
How are you?
Okay.
I show you. Come.
Not like the girls in the USA.
I give you special, crazy fuck.
I make you crazy.
No, no, I don't want to.
Hey, I don't want to do that.
Come on.
Come on inside.
Okay, what you like to call me now?
Hmm?
What you like to call me?
Linda.
Linda?
Just like home.
No, no. Not yet. Not yet.
Come over here.
Call me Linda.
Hey, look. Elephants.
I've got to get an elephant.
No! I can't stay here in a room with a kid crying.
Come over here.
No, no.
Why don't you pay me first? Fuck you!
You seem disturbed.
People inside are doing it for money?
Sometimes a great deal of money.
I cannot play this kind of game myself.
But I'm always... How do you say?
Looking out for those things quite different,
quite rare.
Champagne, perhaps?
No.
Tsk, tsk.
Don't say no.
When a man say no to champagne, he say no to life.
You saw this before?
Up north.
Oh, yes, of course.
I gotta go.
But you must come in.
I insist.
What is there to be afraid of after this war?
War is a joke.
A silly thing.
I'm going home, ace.
Naturellement, I pay my players. Cash.
American.
However, should you prefer German marks,
or perhaps Swiss francs, that,
of course, can be arranged.
I can arrange everything.
You got the wrong guy, ace.
But you must come in.
No, don't do that.
But, I insist.
Nick!
Hey. Nick!
Listen, if you are really brave and lucky,
I can make you very, very rich.
Wow, would you look at that?
Just keep goin'. Just keep goin'.
You said Logan Street though, man.
I just wanna keep goin'. The trailer was right there.
Wait till Michael gets here, huh?
This is it. This is Michael.
All right, everybody, stay where you are.
Stay right there.
I'll go get him. I'll go get him.
Everybody stay here.
Three cheers for the red, white, and blue!
Hip, hip, hurray.
Hip, hip, hurray!
That cab ain't stopping. What's going on?
I can't wait for him to see all this.
What happened?
Hey, Stosh, what happened?
I thought it was him.
So, his plane could be late!
Take it easy will you, Axel?
You're driving everyone nuts.
You okay?
I know Nick will be back soon.
I know Nick. He'll be coming back, too.
Right, Axel?
Fucking A.
Go straight on down to the highway.
It's your bread, man.
Hey, wait!
It's open!
It's...
Michael.
Oh, Michael.
Oh.
Oh, Mich...
Oh, gee.
Gee, you look beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
Let me take your coat.
Boy.
Everybody was here. You missed them all. Oh.
They're gonna be so mad when
they find out they missed you.
Welcome home.
You know, I was hopin'...
I was hopin' somehow, Michael,
maybe you had Nick with you.
No.
Did you hear anything on Nick?
Nothing. He's AWOL. That's all we know.
He'll be back.
He never wrote to me. He never called me.
Well, maybe you were out.
Yeah, maybe.
So how are you, anyway?
I'm fine, okay. How are you?
Uh, me? I'm okay. I'm fine. I go along, you know.
Still working at the market.
There's a million things to do.
Y-You sure you're all right, huh?
Yeah, I'm all right.
What about your wounds?
There's nothing.
Just the usual complications, that's all.
We heard...
No, that's not true. A lot of guys go through it.
Mmm.
I made Nick that sweater.
I couldn't remember the exact size,
but I think he's about the same size as you, huh?
No, too big. Oops.
Well, I could fix that, though.
I mean, one thing about wool, it's really a cinch...
to fix.
Oh, Christ!
It's okay.
How's your job?
Great. Fine, yeah.
Once or twice we almost had to close.
I gotta go to work now.
You gotta go now?
Yes.
Uh, would you mind if I walked you to work?
Mikey, you're so...
weird.
You're always such a gentleman.
It's cold out there.
Yeah.
I'm not used to it.
Oh, I'm so glad you're alive.
I'm so happy.
I really don't know what I feel.
Hello, hi, Mike.
Linda, I just wanted to say
how sorry I am about Nick.
And how...
I know how much you loved him,
and I know that it'll never be the same.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Maybe... I don't know.
Maybe you don't want to talk about it.
How's it going, Hot Lips?
Yeah, no kidding. He's a real tough guy.
It's okay.
Why don't you come in with me?
Just say hello. Come on. Oh, Mike, please.
Just say hello. They want to see you, I know.
Yeah, just for a second, okay? Okay.
Hey, look who's here?
It's Michael!
Look who's here. Hey, everybody.
Oh, Michael, I read about you in the paper.
Oh, Michael.
Oh, Michael. Oh, dear.
Doesn't he look terrific?
What a nice coat you have. Hi, Michael.
Mike. How beautiful you look.
You look good, Mike.
Welcome back.
Doesn't he look gorgeous?
I'm glad he's home.
Hey, wait a minute. Look at this. Medals.
Oh, my god.
All the medals.
Congratulations.
Oh, Michael.
Oh, Helen, come on.
Janie, leave me alone.
We really won over there, huh, Mike? We won.
I have to go to work now.
Good seem' you, Mme.
See you, Michael.
Come see us, Michael.
Can I see you later?
Okay.
After work?
Yeah. Where? Where.
At home? At home? Okay.
One beer at John's. One beer.
What?
Come on, I'll buy you a beer.
All right, just one.
Hey, Axel! Hey, Stosh! Hey, Axel.
Hey!
Hey! He-hey! Look at this!
How you doing?
Mikey! Hey, man, how are you doing? All right.
Hey, where was you? Where was you?
What do you mean, where was I? Where were you?
Where was you, when we had everything all set there.
The beer... I'm I right, Axel? Huh?
I got delayed.
Something...
Hey.
You got a mustache.
Yeah.
Hey, it looks pretty good.
It's cute.
Yeah, it looks...
Come on, we're going to John's.
So, how have you guys been?
Hanging in there. You know?
How does it feel to be shot?
It don't.
Mmm.
It don't hurt, if that's what you want to know.
How you been? Been okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Same old thing, you know?
Nothing's changed.
I'm getting more ass than a toilet seat
and Axel here, he's getting fatter than ever.
Hey, Stan, why don't you show him that gun?
Shh. Take it easy.
That little pussy thing you
carry around, look at that.
Watch it.
What's that for?
Same thing the other one was for.
And what was that for?
He's a worrier.
Ah, forget it. Come on, let's go have a drink.
Yeah, let's get a drink.
Hey, Boom-Boom! Look what I found!
Hey, Michael! Never seen somebody...
Let this man through. A little room!
How you doing, Mike?
What's up, buddy?
Come on, come on, in the back, in the back.
Get in the back.
Come on.
Hey, what's going on here?
Stosh, get the glasses on the sink.
Which ones, the dirty ones?
Yeah, use the dirty ones.
Phew, no shit.
Shit, what did you do?
Win the war all by yourself?
Look at this stuff here.
No help from you.
Here we go!
Misha...
To you, Mike.
To everybody.
Fucking A.
Hey, hey, wait, wait!
To Nick and Steve.
Mmm, mmm.
You look great.
How's Angela?
Not so good, Mike.
Worse since, uh, she talked to him.
Talked to who?
To Steven.
She talked to Steve?
I didn't know he was back.
Oh, you didn't know he's back? Oh, Jesus.
No, I didn't know he was back. Is he back?
You didn't, you didn't...
Where is he? Where is he?
Okay, hey, John, come on. Come on, John.
Where is he? Just answer me. Where is he?
Mike, I don't know. I don't know where he is.
- Just tell me where he is.
- I don't know where he is, Mike.
Angela wouldn't tell us. Angela wouldn't tell us.
She wouldn't talk to anybody.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Boom!
Angela,
I heard Steven was alive. Where is he?
Where is Steven?
Where is he? Just tell me where he is.
Angela, where is Steven?
Just tell me where he is.
Where is he?
Please, you gotta tell me. Now where is he?
Do you know? Where is he?
Take care.
Michael.
Right here.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Just got my gear, and I was gonna go.
What?
I was just gonna go.
No, don't go.
I have, uh, all this food.
I'll make you a nice sit-down dinner.
No, I can't.
Mikey.
Why don't we go to bed?
C-Can't we just comfort each other?
No, I can't. Not here. I gotta get out of here.
Sorry, I just gotta get out.
I'm... I'll be... Look, I don't know...
I feel a lot of distance,
and I feel far away. I'll see you later.
Feels kind of weird,
coming to a motel.
You know what I mean, Michael? Mike?
I gotta put my can down for this one.
Michael, it's on the house.
No, thanks, man.
How you feeling? You okay? I'm feelin' okay.
I'm fine.
You sure?
Yeah.
Yeah!
What do you think of her, Mike?
I don't know.
Huh, no? Come on, on the level.
I don't know, Stosh.
Is she... is she beautiful?
Is she beautiful? Is she?
The truth?
Yeah!
Nope.
No.
Well, do you think she's intelligent?
Neither do I.
I don't think she's intelligent either.
Then what the hell do you see in her?
I don't know. That's what...
I came over to ask you. Maybe she's good in bed.
Why don't you ask her?
Oh, where the fuck is my fucking ball?
Goddamn pinsetter.
Where is he going?
What's he doing?
Axel! Axel!
Michael!
What the hell happened?
The pinsetter came down on him.
Stan, get the jack out of my trunk.
Nothing works around this damn place anymore.
Come on, Axel. We're
gettin' you clear, here.
Watch your... Watch your elbow, there. All right.
You all right, man?
Fucking A!
All right, what do you guys wanna do now, huh?
We're goin' huntin', right?
Who asked you? Who the hell's asking you?
I was askin'... askin' Mike.
Yeah.
He's goin'.
That's right, Mike's going.
But no women.
Just like old times, hey, Mike.
Mike, right? Am I right?
Just like old times.
Fucking A!
Are you kiddin' me, Axel?
Forty times we could've had it,
if I had been where you are!
Go get him, Axel!
Fuck you guys.
How sweet it is.
Fuckin' A.
Jesus Christ! What the hell is that?
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey, John! Hey, Axel! I got one!
Hey, fellas, I got one!
Okay?
Okay!
What's that stupid little gun doin' up here?
In case.
In case? In case of what?
In case you stumble on one of your girlfriends
sucking on a forest ranger's cock?
You say that one more time. Say it!
Go on, say it!
Stanley, you're so full of shit
you're gonna float away.
Try me! You try me! Just say it! Come on. All right.
You're gonna float away.
Easy, Mike.
Take it easy, Mike.
What the hell was that for?
What, you think it was loaded?
Give me that!
You want to play games?
All right, I'll play your fucking games!
Hey!
How do you feel now? Huh? Huh?
Big shot!
Hi, Michael.
Linda's in back.
She's in back?
Yeah, hey, how was the hunting?
It was fine, thanks.
Linda, what's the matter?
I don't know.
What's the matter?
Nothing, I don't know.
Well, it's gotta be something.
I got the car outside.
Yeah. Well, that's okay.
You sure?
No, it's okay. Just leave me alone, okay?
Really.
Good night, see you in the morning.
Good night, see you tomorrow.
Come with me. We'll get you home.
No, I think I'll go with him.
Okay? Thanks. Okay.
You okay?
Did you ever think life would turn out like this?
No.
I-27.
N-40.
Bingo.
We have a bingo, Johnny come lately.
Where are you, Johnny?
There you are.
B-15.
Yeah. I-16.
Right. N-33.
Right.
Z-60.
We have... That's a winner.
Get out of my road there.
Ivan Stivan, I can't see myself smokin'.
And the next number, I-16.
Wish it was I, nice, sweet 16.
I-18. Then you become a man.
Let's go, men, 6-60.
And those boys that can't help themselves,
please, buddy, help them, too.
Oh, will you dance with me?
G-47.
But I'm still satisfied with what I've got.
That wonderful life I've lived.
Think it over, buddy boys, and I'll give you O-61.
Hi, how're you doing?
Steven, there's a call for you.
Maybe it's from Angela.
Hello.
Stevie, it's me, Mike.
Michael?
Hey.
How's things?
I'm okay. Never mind me. How are you?
Great.
Hey, wha... hey, what's that noise?
What?
Oh, wheelchairs.
Hey, Stevie, when are you gettin' out?
Uh, I'm gonna stay here awhile, Mike.
What for?
The place is great.
Huh?
It's like a resort.
I mean, they got basketball,
bowlin'.
What?
Princess Grace came to see us the other day.
Michael?
Hey, hey-
Hey.
Michael.
Steve?
Stevie.
Hey, I gotta go, Mike.
I gotta go.
Curfew, man.
Stevie? Steve?
Mike?
Mike. Hey.
Mike, how are you?
Hey.
Michael.
Good. We made it. We made it.
Okay. Yeah.
Good. That's it.
Hey.
I don't wanna go home.
I know.
Oh, good. Good. I know.
Yeah, good.
I know.
Really.
You look good.
Yeah.
You do any hunting?
Hunting? Yeah, I did hunting. Did you get one?
No, yeah, no, no.
You didn't get a deer?
Didn't get anything. No, I know.
Oh.
I was tracking this beautiful buck
and it slipped away.
Oh.
Angela didn't send you?
Angela?
She didn't send you here?
No.
Yeah, good.
I got something I wanna show you.
What's that?
I got something here.
Come here with me for a minute.
It's something I gotta show you.
Yeah.
Angela, she keeps sending me socks.
It's not socks I gotta show you, Mike.
This... This comes every month from Saigon.
I don't understand.
That place is gonna fall any day now.
It's Nicky, Steve.
Nick's alive?
Mike? Hey.
What did you say?
How do you know?
Hey.
That place is gonna get caught
in a terrible shitstorm.
Where's a guy like Nick get money like this?
I don't know. Cards, maybe.
Listen, Steven, I'm gonna take you home.
Oh, shit, Mike, you promised me.
Stevie, I'm gonna take you home.
Come on. I don't fit... You can't stay here, come on.
Look... Hey.
I'm gonna take you home.
Fuck, man. Look, you promised me, man.
I don't fit! Michael!
Hey, I'm sorry.
You do as your heart tells you, man.
We got a Coke machine, if anybody wants one.
No, Sergeant, we're runnin' late.
Make way!
Hey, where are you going?
Are you going to come with me?
Do you remember me?
You remember me?
You remember Nick? You remember Nick?
Where is he?
I don't know. Really, I don't know.
He disappeared a long time ago.
Hold on a minute.
What are you looking for?
Nothing to see anymore here.
See that?
What you want?
I want a game.
That's for you.
It's too dangerous now.
These times are too dangerous for this kind of game.
What do you think? You think I'm afraid of you?
I want to play the American.
I'll match him. Highest stakes.
Okay.
How do I know you know where he is?
Because I know, that's all.
But I have to take you by the river.
Only because I feel comfortable with the whites.
We are.
You like change your mind? There's still time.
Come on.
Wait here.
He said we have to pay to go inside.
How much?
$1,000.
Tell him I'm coming up.
He said, yes, the famous American is inside.
You have to give him $500 more for this information.
Where's Nick? I don't know.
What do you mean? Where is he?
We have to go ask the boss.
Hey, Nick.
Are you all right?
Nick, it's me.
Nick. Hey. Hey.
What you're doing? Nick? What you're... Oh.
What you're doing?
Nicholas, what's the matter?
Get over there. Get over there.
Do you know it's me? It's Mike.
Tell me, "it's Mike."
Tell me, "it's Mike." It's Mike.
Mike. Mike who?
Mike who? Hey, Mike who?
"Mike who?" I don't know.
Nicholas, I came 12,000 miles back here to get you.
Don't do that to me, I'll fucking... Don't do it.
Don't do it. Don't do it. What's the matter with you?
Don't you recognize me? Huh?
Nicky, I love you.
You're my friend, what are you doing?
How could you fucking do this to me?
You fucking...
Did you hear what I said?
Come here, you fucking guinea.
Salut.
How much?
"How much?" This is how much.
Here, you count it.
C'mon, why not?
Why not?
I don't want this money.
You don't want the money?
Here, take it, take that, too.
Tell him, go ahead.
We don't have much time.
We don't have much time, Nick.
Don't do it.
Is this what you want?
I love you, Nick.
Nicholas.
Come on, Nicky, come home.
Just come home. Home.
Talk to me.
Look, Nicholas, talk to me.
Nicky. Nicky.
Wait a minute. What did you do to your arms?
Nicky, you remember the trees,
all the different ways in the trees.
Remember that? Remember? Huh?
The mountains. You remember all that?
One shot.
One shot. One shot.
Hey.
Yeah.
Nicky! Nick! Nick!
Nicky! Nick!
Nicky. Nicky.
No! Nick! No!
No! No! Nicky! Nick!
This seems to be the last chapter
in the history of American involvement in Vietnam.
It's also been the largest single movement of people
in the history of America itself.
Hillary Brown, ABC News, aboard
the attack aircraft carrier
USS Hancock, in the South China Sea.
Mommy!
I'll get these tables.
Axel, bring... bring those two tables over here.
All right.
Everybody, make yourself at home.
Coffee's already made.
Cups. I'll get the cups.
Oh, yeah, I'll help you with that.
I'll help you, too.
There's too many cups.
How does everybody want their eggs?
I love them scrambled, John.
Toast. Toast.
Hey.
Careful, Linda, it's hot. It's hot.
Hey, Axel, how about some beer?
Here you are.
I'll get started on the eggs.
Yeah, I'll help you with the eggs.
No, Linda. Sit down. Sit down.
Pour the coffee.
It's been such a gray day.
Here's to Nick.
To Nick.
To Nick. To Nick. To Nick. To Nick.